Guide to the University Governance Records: Senate Records 2003-2013 RG3.8 RG 3.8 RG 3.8
Western Connecticut State University Archives and Special Collections
- 2009
  - May 2009
    - GeneralEducation Committee Annual Report for 08/09, May 2009 (Item 306)
    - Graduate Council 07-08, May 2009 (Item 307)
    - Graduate Council 08-09, May 2009 (Item 308)
    - Media Library Services Annual Report for 08/09, May 2009 (Item 309)
    - Physical Working Conditions Annual Report for 08/09, May 2009 (Item 310)
    - Research & Development Application Bylaws Changes, May 2009 (Item 311)
    - Research and Development Committee Annual Report for 08/09, May 2009 (Item 312)
    - Senate Minutes for May 2009 meeting, September 2009 (Item 313)
  - September 2009
    - Agenda, September 2009 (Item 314)
    - IRB Annual Report 2008-2009, September 2009 (Item 315)
    - SGA Circus Resolution, September 2009 (Item 316)
    - Senate Minutes for September 2009 meeting, October 2009 (Item 317)
  - October 2009
    - Agenda, October 2009 (Item 318)
    - EAP AnnualReport 08-09, October 2009 (Item 319)
    - Financial Literacy Proposal, October 2009 (Item 320)
    - ITCBylaw Revision, October 2009 (Item 321)
    - Senate Minutes for October 2009 meeting, December 2009 (Item 322)
  - November 2009
    - Academic Leave Bylaw Revision, November 2009 (Item 323)
    - Agenda, November 2009 (Item 324)
    - GraduateFaculty Criteria, November 2009 (Item 325)
    - GraduateFaculty Criteria - Letter of Introduction, November 2009 (Item 326)
    - ITCBylaw Revision, November 2009 (Item 327)
  - December 2009
    - Agenda, December 2009 (Item 328)
    - Faculty Participation inGraduate Programs, December 2009 (Item 329)
- 2010
  - February 2010
    - Agenda, February 2010 (Item 330)
    - Senate Minutes for February 2010 meeting (Item 331)
    - DraftResolution, February 2010 (Item 332)
    - email, February 2010 (Item 333)
    - Letter A, February 2010 (Item 334)
    - Letter B, February 2010 (Item 335)
    - Senate Minutes for February 2010 meeting (Item 336)
    - P&T Bylaw Revision, February 2010 (Item 337)
  - March 2010
    - Agenda, March 2010 (Item 338)
    - BOT, March 2010 (Item 339)
    - DraftResolution, March 2010 (Item 340)
    - email, March 2010 (Item 341)
    - email, March 2010 (Item 342)
    - Faculty Development Funds Current Application & Instructions, March 2010 (Item 343)
    - Faculty Development Funds Revised Application, March 2010 (Item 344)
    - Senate Minutes for March 2010 meeting (Item 345)
    - Letter A, March 2010 (Item 346)
    - Letter B, March 2010 (Item 347)
    - P&T Bylaw Revision, March 2010 (Item 348)
    - pdf, March 2010 (Item 349)
    - Senate Minutes for March 2010 meeting, May 2010 (Item 350)
  - April 2010
    - Agenda, April 2010 (Item 351)
    - Senate Minutes for April 2010 meeting, May 2010 (Item 352)
    - Senate Minutes for May 2010 meeting, October 2010 (Item 353)
  - May 2010
    - Agenda, May 2010 (Item 354)
  - September 2010
    - Agenda, September 2010 (Item 355)
    - CSU System letter, September 2010 (Item 356)
    - CSU System office document, September 2010 (Item 357)
    - Senate Minutes for September 2010 meeting, October 2010 (Item 358)
  - October 2010
    - Agenda, October 2010 (Item 359)
    - Article IV from BOT bylaws, October 2010 (Item 360)
    - Faculty Senate Comment C, October 2010 (Item 361)
    - Full Time Faculty Search Committee, October 2010 (Item 362)
    - Presidential Search Memo, October 2010 (Item 363)
    - Request for Incomplete Grade, October 2010 (Item 364)
    - Senate Minutes for October 2010 meeting, December 2010 (Item 365)
  - November 2010
    - Agenda, November 2010 (Item 366)
    - CSU AAUP E-Newsletter, November 2010 (Item 367)
    - Faculty Senate Resolution on Emergency Hires, November 2010 (Item 368)
    - Grad Council By-laws Change, November 2010 (Item 369)
    - Proposed Motion for Senate on Incomplete Policy, November 2010 (Item 370)
    - Proposed Motion from Psychology Department, November 2010 (Item 371)
    - Senate Motion for UPBC By-laws revision, November 2010 (Item 372)
    - Senate Minutes for November 2010 meeting, March 2011 (Item 373)
  - December 2010
    - Agenda, December 2010 (Item 374)
    - BasicFacts About In-state Tuition, December 2010 (Item 375)
    - November 2010 Senate Resolutions, December 2010 (Item 376)
    - Statement of Position Regarding the DREAM Act, December 2010 (Item 377)
    - Senate Minutes for December 2010 meeting, March 2011 (Item 378)
- 2011
  - February 2011
    - Agenda, February 2011 (Item 379)
    - Senate Resolutions, November, February 2011 (Item 380)
    - Senate Minutes for February 2011 meeting, March 2011 (Item 381)
  - March 2011
    - Agenda, March 2011 (Item 382)
    - An Act Allowing Children of Undocumented [...], March 2011 (Item 383)
    - Senate Minutes for March 2011 meeting, April 2011 (Item 384)
  - April 2011
    - Agenda, April 2011 (Item 385)
    - Senate Discussion on Class Size (supporting doc), April 2011 (Item 386)
    - Senate Minutes for April 2011 meeting, May 2011 (Item 387)
  - May 2011
    - Agenda, May 2011 (Item 388)
    - CUCAS Report, May 2011 (Item 389)
    - Media andLibrary Services Policy Committee Report, May 2011 (Item 390)
    - P&T Report, May 2011 (Item 391)
    - Physical WorkingConditions Committee Report, May 2011 (Item 392)
    - R&D Report, May 2011 (Item 393)
    - Senate Minutes for May 2011 meeting, September 2011 (Item 394)
  - September 2011
    - Agenda, September 2011 (Item 395)
    - CELT report, September 2011 (Item 396)
    - IHHS report, September 2011 (Item 397)
    - Senate roster, September 2011 (Item 398)
    - UPBC report, September 2011 (Item 399)
    - WIC report, September 2011 (Item 400)
    - Senate Minutes for September 2011 meeting, October 2011 (Item 401)
  - October 2011
    - ACHA Guidelines, October 2011 (Item 402)
    - Agenda, October 2011 (Item 403)
    - Centerfor the Study of Culture and Values Bylaws - Amended, October 2011 (Item 404)
    - Centerfor the Study of Culture and Values Bylaws - Old, October 2011 (Item 405)
    - CNN Report onCollege Smokers/Smoking, October 2011 (Item 406)
    - General EducationCurriculum - Revised, October 2011 (Item 407)
    - Reorganization Planfor Higher Education, October 2011 (Item 408)
    - Smoke-freeColleges and Universities, October 2011 (Item 409)
    - Toll of Tobacco inConnecticut, October 2011 (Item 410)
    - WCSU SmokingPolicy, October 2011 (Item 411)
    - WCSUSmoking Policy - Revised, October 2011 (Item 412)
    - Senate Minutes for October 2011 meeting, November 2011 (Item 413)
  - November 2011
    - Agenda, November 2011 (Item 414)
    - Common Hour,document dated 11/11, November 2011 (Item 415)
    - Common Hourdiscussion, document dated 11/07, November 2011 (Item 416)
    - Senate Minutes for November 2011 meeting, December 2011 (Item 417)
  - December 2011
    - Agenda, December 2011 (Item 418)
    - CELT Bylaws,Current, December 2011 (Item 419)
    - CELT Bylaws,Proposed, December 2011 (Item 420)
    - Senate Minutes for December 2011 meeting, February 2012 (Item 421)
- 2012
  - February 2012
    - Agenda, February 2012 (Item 422)
    - Course Submission Guidelines, Revised, February 2012 (Item 423)
    - SubmittedProposals, New Com 16X Course, February 2012 (Item 424)
    - Transferand Articulation Policy, Proposed, February 2012 (Item 425)
    - Senate Minutes for January 2012 meeting, February 2012 (Item 426)
    - Senate Minutes for February 2012 meeting, March 2012 (Item 427)
  - March 2012
    - Agenda, March 2012 (Item 428)
    - Proposed Transfer and Articulation policy, March 2012 (Item 429)
    - Senate Minutes for March 2012 meeting, April 2012 (Item 430)
  - April 2012
    - Agenda, April 2012 (Item 431)
    - Senate Minutes for April 2012 meeting, May 2012 (Item 432)
  - May 2012
    - Agenda, May 2012 (Item 433)
    - Application guidelines, Summer Curriculum Grants, May 2012 (Item 434)
    - Gen Ed Bylaws, May 2012 (Item 435)
    - P&T Report,2011-2012, May 2012 (Item 436)
    - Senate Minutes for May 2012 meeting, September 2012 (Item 437)
  - September 2012
    - Agenda, September 2012 (Item 438)
    - CELT Annual Report,2011-2012, September 2012 (Item 439)
    - ConnSCU TAP CoreRequirements, September 2012 (Item 440)
    - DistanceEducation Online Policy Draft, September 2012 (Item 441)
    - Faculty Development andRecognition Committee Annual Report, 2011-2012, September 2012 (Item 442)
    - Goals and Outcomesspreadsheet, September 2012 (Item 443)
    - Graduate CouncilAnnual Report, 2011-2012, September 2012 (Item 444)
    - Media and LibraryServices Policy Committee Annual Report, 2011-2012, September 2012 (Item 445)
    - Westside NaturePreserve Annual Report, 2011-2012, September 2012 (Item 446)
    - Senate Minutes for September 2012 meeting, October 2012 (Item 447)
  - October 2012
    - Agenda, October 2012 (Item 448)
    - CUCAS/Grad Council Summary, 2011, October 2012 (Item 449)
    - CUCAS/Grad Council Summary, 2012, October 2012 (Item 450)
    - CUCASAnnual Report, 2011-2012, October 2012 (Item 451)
    - DraftApplication for Reassigned Time, October 2012 (Item 452)
    - EAP AnnualReport, 2011-2012, October 2012 (Item 453)
    - StrategicPlanning Committee Report, October 2012 (Item 454)
    - Senate Minutes for October 2012 meeting, November 2012 (Item 455)
  - November 2012
    - Agenda, November 2012 (Item 456)
    - CCSU Faculty Senate Resolution in Support of BOR Resolution, November 2012 (Item 457)
    - UPBC Bylaws, November 2012 (Item 458)
    - UsingBlackboard for Class Evaluations, November 2012 (Item 459)
    - Senate Minutes for November 2012 meeting, December 2012 (Item 460)
  - December 2012
    - Agenda, December 2012 (Item 461)
    - TAP Steering CommitteeLetter, December 2012 (Item 462)
- 2014 Minutes (audio)
  - Senate meeting, Sep 2014 (Item 4994)
  - Senate meeting, Oct 2014 (Item 4995)
  - Senate meeting, Nov 2014 (Item 4996)
  - Senate meeting, Dec 2014 (Item 4997)
- 2015 Minutes (audio)
  - Senate meeting, Jan 2015 (Item 4998)
  - Senate meeting, Mar 2015 (Item 4999)
  - Senate meeting, Apr 2015 (Item 5000)
  - Senate meeting, May 2015 (Item 5001)
  - Senate meeting, Sep 2015 (Item 5002)
  - Senate meeting, Oct 2015 (Item 5003)
  - Senate meeting, Nov 2015 (Item 5004)
  - Senate meeting, Nov 2015 (Item 5013)
  - Senate meeting, Dec 2015 (Item 5006)
  - Senate meeting, Dec 2015 (Item 5007)
- 2016 Minutes (audio)
  - Senate meeting, Jan 2016 (Item 5008)
  - Senate meeting, Feb 2016 (Item 5009)
  - Senate meeting, Mar 2016 (Item 5010)
  - Senate meeting, Apr 2016 (Item 5011)
  - Senate meeting, May 2016 (Item 5012)
  - Senate meeting, Sep 2016 (Item 4938)
  - Senate meeting, Oct 2016 (Item 4939)
  - Senate meeting, Nov 2016 (Item 4940)
  - Senate meeting, Dec 2016 (Item 4941)
- 2017 Minutes (audio)
  - Senate meeting, Jan 2017 (Item 4942)
  - Senate meeting, Jan 2017 (Item 4943)
  - Senate meeting, Feb 2017 (Item 4944)
  - Senate meeting, Apr 2017 (Item 4945)